#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jasoncrispin (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Banking

Loans Credit

# Jason Crispin

CEO & Owner at The Sportsplex

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

### Summary

Experienced chief executive officer with a demonstrated history of working in the banking, financial and athletics industries. Strong entrepreneurship professional graduated from The University of Texas at Austin - The Red McCombs School of Business.

## Experience

The Sportsplex
CEO & Owner
February 2017 - Present (3 years 6 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Pecantree Capital
President
October 2010 - Present (9 years 10 months)
Dallas, Texas

Texas Sports Center CEO & Owner November 2014 - February 2017 (2 years 4 months) Dallas and Garland

Texas Sports Center will be the largest indoor mulit-sport facility in North Texas. With over 150,000 square feet of indoor sports space, TSC will provide an unparalleled sports experience for youths and adults.

Texas Security Bank Chief Lending Officer & Director April 2007 - January 2009 (1 year 10 months)

- Co-Founded Texas Security Bank.

Bank of Texas President July 2003 - April 2007 (3 years 10 months) Wells Fargo Bank Vice President May 1998 - July 2003 (5 years 3 months)

## Education

The University of Texas at Austin

The University of Texas at Austin - The Red McCombs School of Business
BBA